{
  "data": [
        {
            "question": "___ a democratic revolution took place in Korea.",
            "a": "In Spring of 1980",
            "b": "In a Spring of 1980",
            "c": "In the Spring of 1980",
            "d": "In Springs of 1980",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- The: used to show that you are talking about a particular thing or person\n The spring is determined by year 1980\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "21"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ___ to collect old records.",
            "a": "fun",
            "b": "a fun",
            "c": "the fun",
            "d": "any fun",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Structure: It's adj to do sth",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "21"
        },
        {
            "question": "Taiwan is a small country, but it has ___.",
            "a": "large population",
            "b": "a large population",
            "c": "the large population",
            "d": "large populations",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n-A: used before nouns that are usually uncountable when other information about the quality, feeling etc is added by an adjective, phrase, or\tclause",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "21"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is always off _________ on Saturdays and Sundays.",
            "a": "duty",
            "b": "a duty",
            "c": "the duty",
            "d": "duties",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- Be in/off duty",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "21"
        },
        {
            "question": "The young girls were sitting ___.",
            "a": "a hand in a hand",
            "b": "the hand in a hand",
            "c": "the hand in the hand",
            "d": "hand in hand",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Go/ walk...hand in hand",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "21"
        },
        {
            "question": "When she was charged with murder, she set up ___.",
            "a": "a alibi",
            "b": "an alibi",
            "c": "the alibi",
            "d": "alibi",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\nA/an: used to show that you are referring to a general type of person or thing and not a specific person or thing",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "21"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our teacher is a subscriber to ___.",
            "a": "a New York Times",
            "b": "the New York Times",
            "c": "New York Times",
            "d": "one New York Times",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- Some places and countries, and all rivers and oceans, have the as part of their name\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "21"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was absorbed in listening to Mozart, there was ___ on the door.",
            "a": "knock",
            "b": "a knock",
            "c": "the knock",
            "d": "knocking",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- A: in this case means \"one\"",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "21"
        },
        {
            "question": "We Americans are taught to be very conscious of the passage of time. Such slogans as \" Time is Money\" can often be seen hanging on the walls of many of our factories. Work men are paid ___, and they are constantly reminded that \"every minute counts.\"",
            "a": "by an hour",
            "b": "by hour",
            "c": "by the hour",
            "d": "by the hours",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Pay/charge by the hour (=pay or charge someone according to the number of hours it takes to do something)\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "21"
        },
        {
            "question": "To understand the African, one must get to know him ___. To a greater or lesser degree he will seem to us strange and unattractive, but one must overlook all that and understand his essential nature.",
            "a": "man to man",
            "b": "a man to a man",
            "c": "the man to the man",
            "d": "the man to a man",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Man to man= each person\n- Do not use article before a common noun used in its commonest sense\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "21"
        }
    ]
}